[Music]
[Música]
in yellow I just
en amarillo
uploaded videos videos or
acabo de subir vídeos vídeos o que
was it you who was crying yesterday
fuiste tú que estaba llorando ayer
[Music] I
[Música]
was crying yesterday
estaba llorando ayer por el canal
for the main channel I'm going to abandon them I don't know what to watch a series of multi gamers and I'm in the squid game on the 18th the squid game and I'm training jets or how many hours we were training de paula skipping training anyway
saltándose los entrenamientos en fin
tomorrow we're going to train hard and we're
mañana vamos a entrenar a tope y lo
going to release it in the morning we're going to
vamos a estrenar de la mañana vamos a
streamer the training
streamer el entrenamiento
I just subscribed well welcome
me acabo de suscribir pues bienvenido
done I hope it's forever okay
hecho espero que sea para siempre vale
listen to me family I just uploaded
escúchame familia acabo de subir
the news okay today I uploaded a video the
noticiero vale hoy he subido un vídeo el
main channel for ladies and the video
canal principal para señoras y el vídeo
has exploded okay I'll tell you video
ha reventado vale os comento el vídeo
1 for content and not for the
1 para de contenido y no para el
content but I have to I have to I have to
contenido pero tengo que tengo que tengo
behave like this if I want I want what I
que comportarme así si quiero quiero lo
want the video that is his life each
que quiero el vídeo que es su vida cada
main
principal
5 hours ago has 30 thousand views
hace 5 horas tiene 30 mil visitas
has gained like 300 subscribers to the
ha ganado como 300 suscriptores del
video and has 7,000 light
vídeo y tiene 7.000 light
7000 light okay it's your
7000 light vale
turn to show your face in the
os toca a ustedes dar la cara en el
video of the kids okay it's your turn to
vídeo de la chavalería vale os toca a
show your face
ustedes dar la cara
there you have it the video will hit you in the
ahí lo tenéis el vídeo os tocará en la
face but when I finished
cara pero cuando terminé
watching it turns out that Dallas
a ver resulta ser que está la has dallas
announced that he
ha anunciado qué
wanted to make a movie
que quería hacer una película
that he would like to be a movie okay
que querría ser una película vale
this is a serious question as you know you've been
esto es una pregunta seria como sabéis
telling me for a while that you would
lleváis tiempo diciéndome que os
like me to make a feature film
gustaría que hiciese un largometraje
but seriously I've talked about three newscasts
pero serio he hablado de tres noticieros
but let's come back here and talk a
pero vamos a volver aquí y hablar un
little more extensively okay to upload
poco más extensamente vale para subir
this excerpt to the secondary channel I'm
este extracto al canal secundario yo lo
saying this no joke I mean what it is to
digo fuera de coña o sea lo que es
watch a movie if it doesn't have
a ver una película si no tiene
professionals
profesionales
like summer
como el verano
by the way have you read my mdd instagram I do
por cierto has leído mi mdd instagram
n't know but thanks thanks for the
no lo sé pero gracias gracias por los
vips of course it
vips claro
depends I could stay to see as much as
depende podría quedar a ver tanto como
people were better like that with the laws
la gente era mejor así con lo de leyes
of the queue there are people who do
de la cola hay gente que hace cosas
beautiful things hunger like that on youtube as a rule
guapa hambre así de youtube por norma
but no one who has done anything
pero ninguno que haya hecho una cosa
beautiful but Jordi cool what he did was a
guapa pero jordi guay lo que hizo fue un
short that was well produced at
corto que estuvo bien producido por lo
least although it achieved great things
menos aunque logró fuera la gran cosa
but listen to me what I do believe would
pero escúchame lo que sí que creo que
sell it could even be bought
vendería incluso lo podría comprar
project some brand would be a
proyecto alguna marca sería una docu
docuseries one two because also he says more
serie una dos porque además él dice más
forward that it could be about his life that you
palante que podría ir sobre su vida que
don't know how to invent the script
no sabes inventarse el guión
with the story or about his own life
con la historia o sobre su propia vida
that he has often said hey let's
que muchas veces ha dicho de oye que se
make a movie about the life
haga una película sobre la sobre la vida
of Dallas would not be his mantle don't
de dallas no serían su manto no
listen to me a docuseries in white what has been
escúchame una docu serie en blanco lo
done with dolores back with
que se ha hecho con dolores back que con
models of the milestones bad example because
modelos de los hitos mal ejemplo porque
pathetic is honor to the cherry but well
patético es honor a la cereza pero bueno
in plan in conditions the one of Marta del
en plan en condiciones la de marta del
Castillo had a very good docuseries and in
castillo tuvo muy bien una docu ser y en
plan of 34 chapters that were needed
plan de 34 capítulos que hicieran falta
but also with everything that they have
pero también con todo lo que le han
done to him of everything they have wanted to
hecho de todo lo que han querido
label how they investigated and how they
etiquetar como indagaron y cómo
handled and manipulated here manipulated
manejaron y manipularon aquí manipularon
there to accuse him of one thing and another you
allá para acusarlo de una cosa de otra
know everything well
sabes todo bien
documented and all the roll that would be the
documentado y todo el rollo ese sería la
part truth is one thing happens to him and that is that he does
parte verdad le pasa una cosa y es que
not succeed with the projects he takes on not
no acierta con los proyectos que coge no
to see
a ver
as long as they are some that do not have
mientras que sean algunos que no tengan
large investments then
grandes inversiones pues tampoco pasa
nothing happens but there are some that have had
nada pero hay algunos que han tenido
large investments  that they have been successful
grandes inversiones que han tenido éxito
I believe to recover the investment did not
yo creo para recuperar la inversión ni
even happen to him with a video game he
siquiera le pasó con un videojuego
invested a lot of money to address that he
invirtió mucho dinero a abordar que
invested a lot of money in a video game and it did
invirtió mucho dinero en un videojuego y
not work out and he lost it he just said it is what he
no le salió y lo perdió solo lo dijo es
says it happened to him for not agreeing
lo que lo diga yo le pasó por no acuerdo
okay because there are
vale porque ahí hay
investments that are very complicated they
inversiones que son muy complicadas se
get into very complicated messes that you have to be
meten en líos muy complicados que tiene
very lucky you have to
que tener mucha suerte que tiene que
think about it business are not easy if
pensarlo negocio no son fáciles si todo
everyone knew
el mundo supiera que fuera a salirte
that it was going to turn out well for you an investment for everyone I would say a sure shot but it is playing cloth I do not know what then this is very ambitious some very fanciful I do not know if they will have any investment in a plan simpler more real real I mean with their feet on the ground like hey
refiero con los pies en el suelo en plan
for about three or four businesses
oye por unas tres o cuatro negocios
where you have three or four workers
donde tengáis tres o cuatro trabajadores
in 34 stores that assure me a
en 34 tiendas que me aseguren ahí un
fixed salary per month for not knowing about
sueldo fijo al mes por no saberlo de
YouTube which is what can happen yesterday
youtube que es lo que puede pasar ayer
day tomorrow not
día mañana no
a chain of bars some things but this
una cadena de bares unas cosas pero esto
of if I
de si
proposed to see a well scripted
propusiera a ver bien guionizado un
bus series I think I could almost
autobús serie yo creo que casi lo podría
buy some brand is less them
comprar alguna marca es menos ellos
Netflix would be flipping I know  but many times a
netflix sería flipar sé pero mucha vez
lot of people would see it because what I'm
que lo vería mucha gente porque lo que
telling you maybe the projects have been
te digo a lo mejor los proyectos han
successful but when it comes to
tenido éxito pero cuando se trata de las
his controversies and the stories that
polémicas suyas y de las historias que
have happened to him and the things in his life, you
le han pasado y de las cosas de su vida
know
sabe
people are interested, everyone sees it
la gente le interesa lo ve todo el mundo
when it's things like the dog, the
cuando son cosas de lo del perro de las
complaints of turn of the complaints with
denuncias de su vez de las denuncias con
win michu, when they try those things,
win michu de cuando intentan esas cosas
those videos are seen by everyone
esos vídeos lo ve todo el mundo
so we're talking about something that
entonces estamos hablando ya de una cosa
could have millions
que la podría que podría tener millones
of views worldwide because
de visitas mundial mundialmente porque
we're not talking about a Spanish thing
no estamos hablando de una cosa española
like no, well the pain is back that or he
como no pues el dolor es back que o él
knows would see it, people would see it abroad
sabe lo vería lo vería la gente fuera
but it's a lot of laughter but outside of it, it's
pero es que mucha risa pero fuera
better a movie that
cachondeo para mejor una película que
he makes or a movie that he makes
haga él o sea una película que haga él
inventing the script, inventing
inventándose el guión inventándose
the script and the plot of everything done it wouldn't
el guión y la trama de todo lo hecho no
have as much but if it were about what has
tendría tanto pero si fuera de lo que ha
happened, where he has been through and such
pasado el por donde ha pasado y tal
this could
esto puede
as you know take time telling me
como sabéis llevar el tiempo diciéndome
that you would like me to make a
que os gustaría que hiciese un
feature film but seriously the thing is that
largometraje pero serio la cosa es que
with my reputation I have many doors
con mi reputación tengo muchas puertas
closed forever if they did that
cerradas para siempre si hicieron que
starter
starter
Diego Gracia to produce  a movie would be
diego gracia para producir una peli lo
supported by a lion because look what I
apoyaría un león por fíjate tú que lo
'm saying is a series would
que estoy diciendo es una serie
clean up a lot of image it
limpiaría mucho de imagen
's not a bad idea
no es mala idea
as you see many people asking
como ve a muchas personas haciendo
questions I have written this mini document
preguntas he escrito este mini documento
answering your questions read it and tell me
respondiendo a sus dudas lean y me dicen
if you have any questions by the way if
si les queda alguna duda por cierto si
anyone has worked in v fx within
alguien ha trabajado en v fx dentro de
this I don't understand what it's worth puts
esto no entiendo lo que vale me pone a
a king on replay well here basically
un rey en replay bueno aquí básicamente
apply what a kick starter that you
aplícate lo que un kick starter que
know what it isn't like a crowdfunding a
sabes lo que no es como un crowdfunding
big fan of I do
un gran fan de
n't know what the difference is between a
no sé cuál es la diferencia entre un
click started funding it's the same it
clic started funding es lo mismo no
's not the same no
es lo mismo no
what is the difference it's similar but
cuál es la diferencia es parecido pero
what changes you
qué es lo que cambia
have to change the brand of the name
hay que cambiar la marca del nombre
for what and why not produce or
para qué y por qué no producir o tú
yourself it doesn't make sense to dedicate months
mismo no tiene sentido que dedique meses
of my life to producing a movie if
de mi vida a producir una película si
then people aren't interested in seeing it
luego la gente no le interesa verlo
that would be the best way to see if
esa sería la mejor forma de ver si a la
people are interested in it also with the click
gente le interesa además con el click
starter there would be a digital ticket to
starter vendría una entrada digital para
see it it won't be the same as throwing money
verlo no será lo mismo que tirar dinero
into the air in exchange for nothing obviously
al aire a cambio de nada obviamente
the project of that
el proyecto de eso
the projects that is this art is a
los proyectos eso es este arte es una
company that is dedicated to doing
empresa que se dedica a hacer
crowdfunding okay okay great  let's see
crowdfunding vale vale genial a ver en
what he wants to make sure of is that at
lo que se quiere asegurar es de que por
least he's not going to throw money away,
lo menos no va a tirar el dinero
basically
básicamente
on the logical
en el lógico
if I do it when it's in theaters it's
si lo hago cuando esté en cine no va a
never going to be in theaters we all know the
estar nunca en cine todos sabemos la
horrible reputation I have, that
reputación tan horrible que tengo ese
sector is totally closed to me
sector está totalmente cerrado para mí
forever, the careers of
para siempre se han hundido carreras de
internationally famous actors have been ruined for
actores famosos internacionalmente por
less imagine me
menos imagínense a mí
sad but true well there's no
triste pero cierto bueno no tiene por
reason to look at it they also canceled Johnny
qué mirar el también cancelaron a johnny
Depp they made him look bad everywhere
depp que lo pusieron de maltratado en
and he's back to work and he's back at
y ha vuelto a trabajar y ha vuelto a
Disney
disney
in fact the other day I was in
de hecho el otro día estuve en
Disneyland and in the show I saw
disneylandia y en el espectáculo salí a
Johnny Depp
johnny depp
the show is projected in the castle
el espectáculo proyecta en el castillo
they put Johnny Depp [ __ ] I would be a
pusieron a johnny depp [__] yo sería un
[ __ ] crack
[__] crack
the only viable way to make a
la única forma viable de hacer un
feature film is to self-produce it but it
largometraje es auto producirlo pero
also doesn't make sense to produce something that
tampoco tiene sentido producir algo que
people don't want to see
la gente no quiere ver
I wouldn't get into trouble honestly if
yo no me metería en líos sinceramente si
you feel like doing something that you can
te apetece hacer algo que que puedes
spend or for example make the
gastarte o por ejemplo hacer el kit
arteche kit not the kick starter
arteche no el kick starter
and the money that I get well the one that I
y el dinero que consiga pues el que
have to spend because then here it
tiene para emplear porque luego aquí
is saying that December the best thing
está diciendo que diciembre lo suyo
would be a minimum of  30 thousand the kick
sería un mínimo de 30 mil el kick
starter and me putting in 230 thousand which would be
starter y yo poniendo 230 mil que sería
ideal but I see it difficult so much support
lo ideal pero lo veo difícil tanto apoyo
over 30,000 it is complicated for them to give it to you
sobre 30.000 es complicado que te lo den
but
pero
[Music]
[Música]
I would not get into other types of
yo no me metería en otros tipos de
businesses since you make two or three
negocios ya ti hace dos o tres
investments that are really serious, really serious I
inversiones en plan serias en plan sería
mean that are not so fabulous you
me refiero que no sean tan fabulosas
know like three or four things that I tell you
sabes en plan tres o cuatro cosas que te
60 thousand euros seems little for a
60 mil euros parece poco para una
film I don't know
película no sé
but things can be done and you want to release
pero se pueden hacer cosas y desea salir
things on a small budget it depends on what you
cosas con poco presupuesto depende lo
do but
que hagas pero qué
what good is the solution that I do it
qué bueno es la solución que le lo haga
and nothing just published this if you ask for
y nada acaba de publicar esto si pides
a package maybe mine will arrive it
un paquete a lo mejor te llega el mío se
seems that everything is too small for me
ve que todo me queda pequeño
and nothing I bet he had
y nada que apuesto a que ha tenido
problems again with the one who was
problemas otra vez con el que estaba
creating funds or in other words very bad luck no
creando fondos o sea malísima suerte no
this is the never ending story for the
esto es el cuento de nunca acabar por
third time in a row the
tercera vez consecutiva el programador
Fulham 12 programmer disappeared from the
del fulham 12 volvió a desaparecer de la
face of the earth again and did not respond again it
faz de la tierra y no volvió a responder
is paid at the end of the project send
es pagado al terminar el proyecto manda
your unity video games
tus juegos en vídeo
to programmers and explain the
a programadores tal y explica la
experience more information in case you
experiencia más información por si
want to work with me creating
quieres trabajar conmigo creando
video games  it's not a one time thing
videojuegos no es algo de una sola vez
if you work with fort font 2 there will be more
si funcionas con fort font 2 habrá más
work for you 100% and I offer that you
trabajo para ti 100% y ofrezco que te
can dedicate yourself to it professionally
puedas dedicar a ello profesionalmente
only people would be mandatory to send look
solo gente sería obligatorio mandar mira
for example these little things about
por ejemplo estas cosillas de los
video games
videojuegos
the other times it went wrong I do
las otras veces le salió mal
n't know how that ended and he made a video
no sé en qué quedó eso y él hizo vídeo
saying that he lost a lot of money but
diciendo que perdía mucho dinero pero
that a youtube was gas and video games and
que un youtube era gas y videojuegos y
things sites if I don't see it
cosas sitios si no veo
I do see it too not on youtube the
yo si lo veo también no en youtube de la
size of dallas
talla de dallas tal
but thanks to an investment too too
pero gracias a una inversión demasiado
too powerful because
demasiado demasiado potente porque
because a youtuber has his followers
porque un youtuber tiene sus seguidores
and makes a game that people like he
y se hace un juego que pueda gustar
can sell it he
lo puede vender
Joan Plana should direct the movie
joan plana debería dirigir la película
given by god we want Dallas to do well
dado por dios queremos que le vaya bien
look at the fernanflor final flash here two
mira el fernanflor final flash acá dos
video games of that no and I mobile video games
videojuegos de eso no y yo videojuegos
but there are also things that I think it's
pero también hay cosas que yo creo que
the sas it's more for illusion than for
es la sas es más por ilusión que por
money because in the end I think that many
dinero pues al final yo creo que muchas
things that something blows his mind he does
cosas que alguna cosa le reviente le
well of course but what
vaya bien por supuesto pero que también
I also see is that he does things that he
yo lo que veo es que hace cosas que a él
likes out of illusion they are things that he
le gustan por ilusión son cosas que él
are things that are complicated that  succeed
son cosas que son complica que triunfe
but he does it because he comes up with
pero que las hace porque se le ocurren
ideas and he has the illusion, he releases a
las ideas y las ilusión saca un
mobile video game javi well paula
videojuego de móvil javi bueno paula
look at what these people say we pay attention to it
mira lo que dicen esta gente lo hacemos
no
caso no
[Music]
[Música]